<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>LED Headlights on Bharat growth Consultants</title>
    <link>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/surgical/led-headlights/</link>
    <description>Recent content in LED Headlights on Bharat growth Consultants</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 13:08:13 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/surgical/led-headlights/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>High Intensity HDi</title>
      <link>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/surgical/led-headlights/high-itensity-hdi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/surgical/led-headlights/high-itensity-hdi/</guid>
      <description>Choose 100,000 LUX or 140,000 LUX of HDi uniform light distribution powered by HDi Universal Power Packs with simple one-touch operation.
LED DayLite® HDi 100,000 LUX Output with HDi uniform light distribution
Versatile and Modular easily clips onto Loupes or Headband
Coaxial to Your Line of Sight Custom position and lock the headlight coaxial to your line of sight
HDi Universal Power Pack (more info) with simple one-touch operation and smart-link technology for long procedures</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LED DayLite® UltraMini HDi</title>
      <link>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/surgical/led-headlights/led-daylite-ultramini-hdi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/surgical/led-headlights/led-daylite-ultramini-hdi/</guid>
      <description>NEW High Definition Imaging Technology – HDi Patent pending advanced photonic design provides a uniform field of light distribution with fiberoptic quality light. MORE INFO 45% More Light with HDi&amp;rsquo;s optically focused LED Lightweight and Modular Weighing in at a half an ounce, the LED DayLite Ultra Mini is the lightest surgical headlight. Convenient T-mount easily clips onto your telescopes, glasses or lightweight headband.
Fits under most Face Shields Adjustable Light Intensity – Neutral WHITE (5800° K) light.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Micro Series HDi Headlights</title>
      <link>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/surgical/led-headlights/micro-series-hdi-headlights/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/surgical/led-headlights/micro-series-hdi-headlights/</guid>
      <description>Lightweight modular headlights with innovative power packs provide 55,000 lux high intensity and 30,000 lux medium intensity of HDi uniform light distribution (HDi US Patent 8,851,709)
LED DayLite® Micro HDi High Definition Imaging – HDi uniform light distribution with 45% more light
Lightweight, Modular Design – clips onto your existing loupes
Micro Power Pack (2.5 oz.) with up to 10 hour run time per pack and low battery indication
Simple One-Touch Operation: 55,000 lux high intensity, 30,000 lux medium intensity</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEW DayLite® HDi</title>
      <link>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/surgical/led-headlights/new-daylite-hdi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/surgical/led-headlights/new-daylite-hdi/</guid>
      <description>NEW High Definition Imaging Technology – HDi Patent pending advanced photonic design provides uniform light distribution with fiberoptic quality light. MORE INFO 45% More Light with HDi&amp;rsquo;s optically focused LED Adjustable Light Intensity of Neutral WHITE (5800° K) light.
Coaxial to Your Line of Sight Easily position light optic to your line of sign
Modular and Lightweight T-mount easily clips onto your telescopes or a lightweight headband
Two HDi Universal Power Packs with ONE TOUCH operation, ROBUST USB connections, FUEL GAUGE, User replaceable LI-ION BATTERY, and SMART-LINK capability to extend battery life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEW High Definition Imaging – HDi</title>
      <link>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/surgical/led-headlights/new-high-definition-imaging/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/surgical/led-headlights/new-high-definition-imaging/</guid>
      <description>NEW High Definition Imaging – HDi Introducing HDi&amp;rsquo;s advanced photonic design providing uniform light distribution with fiber optic quality light. The entire LED DayLite® series of headlights, Corded and WireLess, are now equipped with HDi technology providing 45% more light and increased modularity.
HDi - High Definition Imaging HDI with optically focused LED Uniform Light Distribution advanced photonic design perfectly images LED for uniform light distribution with maximum intensity
More Illumination optically focused LED provides 45% more light</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEW LED DayLite® Twin Beam® HDi</title>
      <link>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/surgical/led-headlights/new-led-daylite-twin-beam-hdi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/surgical/led-headlights/new-led-daylite-twin-beam-hdi/</guid>
      <description>NEW High Definition Imaging Technology – HDi Patent pending advanced photonic design provides uniform light distribution with fiberoptic quality light. MORE INFO 45% More Light with HDi&amp;rsquo;s optically focused LED
Optically Collimated to Maximize Range of Light Patented collimated design maximizes light intensity while maintaining 5800°K neutral WHITE color temperature.
Modular T-mount enables you to easily clip light optics onto your personal headband of choice
Coaxial to Your Line of Sight New double knuckle hinge allows you to custom position and lock the headlight coaxial to your line of sight</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Surgical Literature</title>
      <link>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/surgical/led-headlights/surgical-literature/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/surgical/led-headlights/surgical-literature/</guid>
      <description> NEWREVEALTM FGS WEARABLE Fluorescence Guided System SURGICAL MAGNIFICATION NEW Panoramic Loupes LED DayLite® with NEW HDi technology for uniform light distribution and fiber optic quality light NEW MODULAR LED DayLite NanoCamHDi with DBR software </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wireless HDi Highlights</title>
      <link>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/surgical/led-headlights/wireless-hdi-highlights/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/surgical/led-headlights/wireless-hdi-highlights/</guid>
      <description>WireLess HDi Headlights LED DayLite® WireLess headlights are equipped with HDi&amp;rsquo;s advanced photonic design providing uniform light distribution and 45% more light. (HDi US Patent 8,851,709)
LED DayLite® WireLess Mini HDi High Definition Imaging – HDi: Uniform light distribution with 45% more light
Totally WireLess – no cords, no battery pack Modular Design – clips onto your existing loupes Lightweight (1 oz) 34,000 lux intensity The LED DayLite® WireLess Mini HDi, a self-contained totally cord-free headlight with HDi technology.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
