<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bharat growth Consultants</title><link>http://vipatra.in/</link><description>Recent content on Bharat growth Consultants</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 13:08:13 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://vipatra.in/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Customer Care</title><link>http://vipatra.in/customer-service/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 13:35:51 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://vipatra.in/customer-service/</guid><description>Phone: +91-22-22062616
Email: bharatgrowthconsultants@gmail.com
Address: 419/D Joshi Wadi Kalabadevi Rao, Mumbai</description></item><item><title>Nano Cam Hdi</title><link>http://vipatra.in/surgical/nano-cam-hdi/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 13:08:13 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://vipatra.in/surgical/nano-cam-hdi/</guid><description>NEW LED DayLite® NanoCam HDiTM DOCUMENT Easy to use, hands-free operation. Digitally insert 1080p HiDef video and images into patient record
BROADCAST Transmit real time first person view to entire surgical team
RECORD Record Surgeon&amp;rsquo;s point of view – an invaluable tool for instruction. NEW easy to use DBR software with HIPAA compliance and 24/7 support
SPECIFICATIONS Camera
1080p high definition 30fps fixed frame rate 24 bit color
Auto exposure Lockable camera focus Aircraft grade aluminum</description></item><item><title>Magnification</title><link>http://vipatra.in/dental/magnification/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 00:51:42 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://vipatra.in/dental/magnification/</guid><description>Standard Field Dental Telescopes True Magnification The purpose of Dental Telescopes is to enhance or magnify an image to insure the highest quality results in dental procedures. We take our responsibility to dentists and their patients seriously so all of our Dental Telescopes provide the TRUE magnification that is expected.
Exclusive Telescope Design with Precision Coated Optics for the best possible vision through the lens and easy peripheral vision around the telescope, allowing you to switch from magnified to unmagnified viewing of the field without needing a third hand to remove or manipulate the telescopes.</description></item><item><title>Magnification</title><link>http://vipatra.in/surgical/magnification/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 00:51:42 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://vipatra.in/surgical/magnification/</guid><description>Standard Field Dental Telescopes True Magnification The purpose of Dental Telescopes is to enhance or magnify an image to insure the highest quality results in dental procedures. We take our responsibility to dentists and their patients seriously so all of our Dental Telescopes provide the TRUE magnification that is expected.
Exclusive Telescope Design with Precision Coated Optics for the best possible vision through the lens and easy peripheral vision around the telescope, allowing you to switch from magnified to unmagnified viewing of the field without needing a third hand to remove or manipulate the telescopes.</description></item><item><title>Hygienists</title><link>http://vipatra.in/dental/hygienists/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 00:51:03 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://vipatra.in/dental/hygienists/</guid><description>NEW Micro2.5x ScopesTM True 2.5X Magnification Though some companies claim that magnification is not important, it is the most important feature of a magnification system. A system that magnifies the image only 2.0x reduces the users ability to visualize structures by a factor of 25%. Designs for Vision produces accurate precision magnification with maximum resolution.
Thru-the-Lens (TTL) Optics This lightweight system provides the Widest Field of View
Ergonomically Correct – Made for YOUR eyes ONLY Built to your Interpupillary Distance instead of one size fits all, these telescopes Incorporate your eyeglass prescription into both the carrier lens and the telescope.</description></item><item><title>HDi</title><link>http://vipatra.in/surgical/hdi/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 00:50:30 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://vipatra.in/surgical/hdi/</guid><description>NEW High Definition Imaging – HDi Introducing HDi&amp;rsquo;s advanced photonic design providing uniform light distribution with fiber optic quality light. The entire LED DayLite series of headlights are now equipped with HDi technology providing 45% more light and increased modularity.
BRILLIANT HDi&amp;rsquo;s advanced photonic design provides 45% more light with an even field of illumination
MODULAR The HDi Universal Power Pack recognizes and operates each HDi series headlight. Each HDi headlight can easily be moved to and from the magnification or headset you select for a particular procedure</description></item><item><title>Optics and Ergonomics</title><link>http://vipatra.in/dental/optics-and-ergonomics/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 00:50:30 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://vipatra.in/dental/optics-and-ergonomics/</guid><description>Designed and Manufactured Thru-the-Lens (TTL) Why Thru-the-Lens Magnification? Increases Field Size Reduces Weight Eliminates Hardware that causes telescopes to come out of alignment Why Designs for Vision’s Thru-the-Lens Magnification? Optically Aligned to YOUR Interpupillary Distance Measurement – ensures you are looking through the optical center of the telescopes, providing better vision
Unique Shape allows for better intraoral vision Exclusively designed, engineered and manufactured Easier Peripheral Vision and Better Ergonomics due to telescopes lower position relative to eye</description></item><item><title>Optics and Ergonomics</title><link>http://vipatra.in/surgical/optics-and-ergonomics/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 00:50:30 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://vipatra.in/surgical/optics-and-ergonomics/</guid><description>Designed and Manufactured Thru-the-Lens (TTL) Why Thru-the-Lens Magnification? Increases Field Size Reduces Weight Eliminates Hardware that causes telescopes to come out of alignment Why Designs for Vision’s Thru-the-Lens Magnification? Optically Aligned to YOUR Interpupillary Distance Measurement – ensures you are looking through the optical center of the telescopes, providing better vision
Unique Shape allows for better intraoral vision Exclusively designed, engineered and manufactured Easier Peripheral Vision and Better Ergonomics due to telescopes lower position relative to eye</description></item><item><title>High Intensity HDi</title><link>http://vipatra.in/dental/led-headlights/hight-intensity-hdi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://vipatra.in/dental/led-headlights/hight-intensity-hdi/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Micro HDi</title><link>http://vipatra.in/dental/led-headlights/micro-hdi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://vipatra.in/dental/led-headlights/micro-hdi/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Wireless HDi</title><link>http://vipatra.in/dental/led-headlights/wireless-hdi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://vipatra.in/dental/led-headlights/wireless-hdi/</guid><description>WireLess HDi Headlights LED DayLite® WireLess headlights are equipped with HDi&amp;rsquo;s advanced photonic design providing uniform light distribution and 45% more light. (HDi US Patent 8,851,709)
LED DayLite® WireLess Mini HDi High Definition Imaging – HDi: Uniform light distribution with 45% more light
Totally WireLess – no cords, no battery pack Modular Design – clips onto your existing loupes Lightweight (1 oz) 34,000 lux intensity The LED DayLite® WireLess Mini HDi, a self-contained totally cord-free headlight with HDi technology.</description></item></channel></rss>