<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nano Cam Hdi on Bharat growth Consultants</title>
    <link>http://vipatra.in/surgical/nanocam-hdi.md/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nano Cam Hdi on Bharat growth Consultants</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 13:08:13 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://vipatra.in/surgical/nanocam-hdi.md/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HDi-Advantage</title>
      <link>http://vipatra.in/surgical/nanocam-hdi.md/hdi-advantage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vipatra.in/surgical/nanocam-hdi.md/hdi-advantage/</guid>
      <description>NEW High Definition Imaging – HDi Introducing HDi&amp;rsquo;s advanced photonic design providing uniform light distribution with fiber optic quality light. The entire LED DayLite series of headlights are now equipped with HDi technology providing 45% more light and increased modularity.
BRILLIANT HDi&amp;rsquo;s advanced photonic design provides 45% more light with an even field of illumination
MODULAR The HDi Universal Power Pack recognizes and operates each HDi series headlight. Each HDi headlight can easily be moved to and from the magnification or headset you select for a particular procedure</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LED DayLite® WireLess IR HDi Procedural Light</title>
      <link>http://vipatra.in/surgical/nanocam-hdi.md/led-daylite-wireless-ir-hdi-procedural-light/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vipatra.in/surgical/nanocam-hdi.md/led-daylite-wireless-ir-hdi-procedural-light/</guid>
      <description>LED DayLite® WireLessIR HDi NEW HDi – High Definition Imaging Technology Patent pending advanced photonic design provides a uniform field of light distribution with fiberoptic quality light.
Totally Wire Free and Self Contained - No cords, no battery pack
Intuitive Response (IR) Touch-Free Operation - Operates with a wave of hand to maintain sterility
Modular Design - clips onto your existing loupes!
Weighs ONLY 1.4 oz. Perfect for In-Office Procedures Patented Technology: 8,851,709 RE46,463 9,791,138</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEW LED DayLite® Twin Beam® HDi</title>
      <link>http://vipatra.in/surgical/nanocam-hdi.md/new-led-daylite-twin-beam-hdi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vipatra.in/surgical/nanocam-hdi.md/new-led-daylite-twin-beam-hdi/</guid>
      <description>NEW High Definition Imaging Technology – HDi Patent pending advanced photonic design provides uniform light distribution with fiberoptic quality light. MORE INFO 45% More Light with HDi&amp;rsquo;s optically focused LED
Optically Collimated to Maximize Range of Light Patented collimated design maximizes light intensity while maintaining 5800°K neutral WHITE color temperature.
Modular T-mount enables you to easily clip light optics onto your personal headband of choice
Coaxial to Your Line of Sight New double knuckle hinge allows you to custom position and lock the headlight coaxial to your line of sight</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
