<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Magnification on Bharat growth Consultants</title>
    <link>http://vipatra.in/surgical/magnification/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Magnification on Bharat growth Consultants</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://vipatra.in/surgical/magnification/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Expanded Field Dental Telescopes</title>
      <link>http://vipatra.in/surgical/magnification/expanded-field-dental-telescopes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vipatra.in/surgical/magnification/expanded-field-dental-telescopes/</guid>
      <description>Provide a 50% increase in the Field of View over the Standard Field of the same magnification. These Dental Telescopes provide crisp side to side imaging for procedures where a wider field of view is required.
Custom Made to Each Individual Each pair of telescopes is individually manufactured to rigorous standards. The focal length is set to your exact working distance, (not simply small, medium or long), The only way to build an ergonomically correct system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frame Selection Guide</title>
      <link>http://vipatra.in/surgical/magnification/frame-selection-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vipatra.in/surgical/magnification/frame-selection-guide/</guid>
      <description>NEW Disinfection Information: NEW Disinfectable Eyewear Retainers available for your Loupes
Disinfecting Instructions for Loupes and Headlights</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laser Telescopes</title>
      <link>http://vipatra.in/surgical/magnification/laser-telescopes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vipatra.in/surgical/magnification/laser-telescopes/</guid>
      <description>Designed exclusively for use with the Solea Dental Laser Patented Dual Lens Design so laser is filtered twice. Two absorptive Polymer Lenses filter the laser before and after magnification. All filters, in both telescopes and carrier lens, block Solea&amp;rsquo;s unique 9.3 µm wavelength.
Absorptive Polymer Wrap-Around Lens provides lateral protection in carrier lens while retaining peripheral vision. All aircragt grade aluminum frame for durability and comfort.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magnification</title>
      <link>http://vipatra.in/surgical/magnification/standard-fiels-dental-telescopes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vipatra.in/surgical/magnification/standard-fiels-dental-telescopes/</guid>
      <description>Standard Field Dental Telescopes True Magnification The purpose of Dental Telescopes is to enhance or magnify an image to insure the highest quality results in dental procedures. We take our responsibility to dentists and their patients seriously so all of our Dental Telescopes provide the TRUE magnification that is expected.
Exclusive Telescope Design with Precision Coated Optics for the best possible vision through the lens and easy peripheral vision around the telescope, allowing you to switch from magnified to unmagnified viewing of the field without needing a third hand to remove or manipulate the telescopes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Micro 2.5x Scopes</title>
      <link>http://vipatra.in/surgical/magnification/new-micro2.5x-scopes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vipatra.in/surgical/magnification/new-micro2.5x-scopes/</guid>
      <description>23% Smaller, 36% Lighter allowing for increased peripheral vision and lightweight comfort
True 2.5x Magnification Engineered for dentists and hygienists that require true 2.5X magnification, but request a lighter, smaller device.
Ergonomically Correct – Made for YOUR eyes ONLY Designs for Vision matches the focal length of each telescope to YOUR ideal working distance, customizing the depth of focus for maximum ergonomics.
Unmatched Quality and Performance Precision coated for the sharpest and clearest magnified image - Better than HD they are precision optics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEW MicroEF Scopes</title>
      <link>http://vipatra.in/surgical/magnification/new-micro-ef-scopes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vipatra.in/surgical/magnification/new-micro-ef-scopes/</guid>
      <description>Revolutionary Prismatic Design
Up to 50% Smaller Up to 44% Lighter Designs for Vision Custom Optics with rectangular shape for maximum peripheral vision.
Provide a 50% increase in the Field of View over the Standard Field of the same magnification. These Surgical Telescopes provide crisp side to side imaging for procedures where a wider field of view is required.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Panoramic Loupes</title>
      <link>http://vipatra.in/surgical/magnification/new-panoramic-loupes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vipatra.in/surgical/magnification/new-panoramic-loupes/</guid>
      <description>See Beyond Expanded Field Loupes See BEYOND expanded field with the patented panoramic design – the first advancement in telescopic optics in 100 years
Doubles the Viewable Area over Prismatic Expanded Field optics, and more than quadruples the viewable area over Galilean Standard Field optics
3.5x and 4.5x Precision Magnification available with unprecedented fields of view
Designs for Vision Custom Optics with crisp side to side imaging and rectangular shape for maximum peripheral vision</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Safety Scopes</title>
      <link>http://vipatra.in/surgical/magnification/safety-scopes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vipatra.in/surgical/magnification/safety-scopes/</guid>
      <description>Offers Protection from both UV and blue light (530 nm and below) emitted from curing lights.
Patented Design Exclusively Available on all Designs for Vision, Inc. dental telescopes. Custom Made to Doctor&amp;rsquo;s specific measurements and prescription.
Eliminates Changing Protective Devices, aiding in infection control.
Choice of Positioning Protective segment may be placed at top or bottom of carrier lens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thru-the-Lens(TTL) Telescopes</title>
      <link>http://vipatra.in/surgical/magnification/thru-the-lens-ttl-telescopes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vipatra.in/surgical/magnification/thru-the-lens-ttl-telescopes/</guid>
      <description>Why Thru-the-Lens Magnification? Increases Field Size
Reduces Weight Eliminates Hardware that causes telescopes to come out of alignment
Why Designs for Vision’s Thru-the-Lens Magnification? Optically Aligned to YOUR Interpupillary Distance Measurement – ensures you are looking through the optical center of the telescopes, providing better vision
Unique Shape allows for better intraoral vision
Exclusively designed, engineered and manufactured
Easier Peripheral Vision and Better Ergonomics due to telescopes lower position relative to eye</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
