<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Optics and Ergonomics on Bharat growth Consultants</title>
    <link>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/optics-and-ergonomics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Optics and Ergonomics on Bharat growth Consultants</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/optics-and-ergonomics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/optics-and-ergonomics/truth-in-magnification/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/optics-and-ergonomics/truth-in-magnification/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dental Loupes</title>
      <link>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/optics-and-ergonomics/dental-loupes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/optics-and-ergonomics/dental-loupes/</guid>
      <description>Custom Crafted Dental Loupes (Telescopes) Thru-the-Lens Design pioneered by Designs for Vision
Provides the Widest Field of View Lightest Weight System
Made for YOUR eyes ONLY Built to your Interpupillary Distance instead of one size fits all
Incorporates your Eyeglass Prescription into both the carrier lens and the telescope
Unmatched Quality and Performance World&amp;rsquo;s Leading Manufacturer of Dental Loupes
Dependable, Precise Dental Vision
Sharpest and Clearest Magnified Image
Excellent Peripheral Vision around uniquely shaped telescope</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Precision Coated Optics</title>
      <link>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/optics-and-ergonomics/precision-coated-optics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/optics-and-ergonomics/precision-coated-optics/</guid>
      <description>Designs for Vision’s multilayer precision coatings utilize our proprietary process to transmit 99.5% of light entering the telescope (reflecting less than 0.5% of light), providing brighter and crisper vision than competitive products. Increased Light Transmission also produces enhanced Depth of Field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thru-the-Lens(TTL) Telescopes</title>
      <link>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/optics-and-ergonomics/thru-the-lens-ttl-telescopes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/optics-and-ergonomics/thru-the-lens-ttl-telescopes/</guid>
      <description>Why Thru-the-Lens Magnification? Increases Field Size
Reduces Weight Eliminates Hardware that causes telescopes to come out of alignment
Why Designs for Vision’s Thru-the-Lens Magnification? Optically Aligned to YOUR Interpupillary Distance Measurement – ensures you are looking through the optical center of the telescopes, providing better vision
Unique Shape allows for better intraoral vision
Exclusively designed, engineered and manufactured
Easier Peripheral Vision and Better Ergonomics due to telescopes lower position relative to eye</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TRUE Magnification Matters!</title>
      <link>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/optics-and-ergonomics/true-magnification-matters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/optics-and-ergonomics/true-magnification-matters/</guid>
      <description>Designs for Vision has delivered TRUE Magnification since 1961 and we are accustomed to delivering the quality that is expected in dentistry. We believe that a 2.5X product should increase the image size 2.5 times. Though some companies claim that magnification is not important, it is the most important feature, enabling the dental professional to see better. A loupe that magnifies the image only 2.0x reduces the users ability to visualize structures by a factor of 25%.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
