<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hygienists on Bharat growth Consultants</title>
    <link>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/hygienists/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hygienists on Bharat growth Consultants</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/hygienists/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2.5x Designer Telescopes</title>
      <link>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/hygienists/2.5x-designer-telescopes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/hygienists/2.5x-designer-telescopes/</guid>
      <description>True 2.5X Magnification Though some companies claim that magnification is not important, it is the most important feature of a magnification system. A system that magnifies the image only 2.0x reduces the users ability to visualize structures by a factor of 25%. Designs for Vision produces accurate precision magnification with maximum resolution.
Thru-the-Lens (TTL) Optics This lightweight system provides the Widest Field of View
Ergonomically Correct – Made for YOUR eyes ONLY Built to your Interpupillary Distance instead of one size fits all, these telescopes Incorporate your eyeglass prescription into both the carrier lens and the telescope.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BDR Loupes</title>
      <link>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/hygienists/bdr-loupes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/hygienists/bdr-loupes/</guid>
      <description>
Best Resolution Our precision coated optics with true magnification reduces eye strain by providing the best resolution and&amp;hellip;
Greatest Depth of Field Contributing to the prevention of neck and lower back pain. Widest Field of View BDR Loupes provide TRUE Magnification and the widest field of view.
Unobstructed View We manufacture the only rectangular optics providing an unobstructive view.
Lightest Weight Comfortable, Hypoallergenic, Lightweight Frames
Easiest to Clean </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dental Literature</title>
      <link>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/hygienists/dental-literature/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/hygienists/dental-literature/</guid>
      <description>DENTAL MAGNIFICATION: NEW Panoramic Loupes NEW MicroSeries Scopes Custom Dental Telescopes NEW REVEAL Introducing hands-free fluorescence in dentistry NEW LED DayLite® High Definition Imaging HDi Series Headlights - WireLess Mini HDi - NEW WireLess IR HDi - NEW Micro IR HDi Nike Frame Selection Guide Award Winning Products &amp; Frame Selection Guide There&#39;s More to Magnification than Meets the Eye A practical guide designed to provide dental professionals with sufficient optical information to select an ergonomically correct telescope system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expanded Field Dental Telescopes</title>
      <link>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/hygienists/expanded-field-dental-telescopes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/hygienists/expanded-field-dental-telescopes/</guid>
      <description>Provide a 50% increase in the Field of View over the Standard Field of the same magnification. These Dental Telescopes provide crisp side to side imaging for procedures where a wider field of view is required.
Custom Made to Each Individual Each pair of telescopes is individually manufactured to rigorous standards. The focal length is set to your exact working distance, (not simply small, medium or long), The only way to build an ergonomically correct system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frame Selection Guide</title>
      <link>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/hygienists/frame-selection-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/hygienists/frame-selection-guide/</guid>
      <description>NEW Disinfection Information: NEW Disinfectable Eyewear Retainers available for your Loupes
Disinfecting Instructions for Loupes and Headlights
For more info click here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HDi Headlights</title>
      <link>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/hygienists/hdi-headlights/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/hygienists/hdi-headlights/</guid>
      <description>NEW High Definition Imaging – HDi Introducing HDi&amp;rsquo;s advanced photonic design providing uniform light distribution with fiber optic quality light. The entire LED DayLite® series of headlights, Corded and WireLess, are now equipped with HDi technology providing 45% more light and increased modularity.
HDi - High Definition Imaging HDI with optically focused LED Uniform Light Distribution advanced photonic design perfectly images LED for uniform light distribution with maximum intensity
LED DayLite® WireLess Mini HDi High Definition Imaging – HDi uniform light distribution with 45% more light</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laser Telescopes</title>
      <link>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/hygienists/laser-telescopes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/hygienists/laser-telescopes/</guid>
      <description>Designed exclusively for use with the Solea Dental Laser Patented Dual Lens Design so laser is filtered twice. Two absorptive Polymer Lenses filter the laser before and after magnification. All filters, in both telescopes and carrier lens, block Solea&amp;rsquo;s unique 9.3 µm wavelength.
Absorptive Polymer Wrap-Around Lens provides lateral protection in carrier lens while retaining peripheral vision. All aircragt grade aluminum frame for durability and comfort.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Micro 2.5x Scopes</title>
      <link>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/hygienists/new-micro2.5x-scopes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/hygienists/new-micro2.5x-scopes/</guid>
      <description>23% Smaller, 36% Lighter allowing for increased peripheral vision and lightweight comfort
True 2.5x Magnification Engineered for dentists and hygienists that require true 2.5X magnification, but request a lighter, smaller device.
Ergonomically Correct – Made for YOUR eyes ONLY Designs for Vision matches the focal length of each telescope to YOUR ideal working distance, customizing the depth of focus for maximum ergonomics.
Unmatched Quality and Performance Precision coated for the sharpest and clearest magnified image - Better than HD they are precision optics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEW Aerosol Protection Loupes</title>
      <link>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/hygienists/new-aerosol-protection-loupes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/hygienists/new-aerosol-protection-loupes/</guid>
      <description>Silicone eyecup creates a seal around your eyes to protect against aerosols
Aerosol Protection Loupes provide adjustable spring hinges and wire core temples to ensure a secure adjustable fit.
Removeable Silicone Eyecups are soft, lightweight and comfortable and provide a complete orbital sealing fit. They attach to the frame magnetically and are easy to remove for cleaning and disinfecting.
Aerosol Protection Loupes are available in 2.5x, 3.0x and 3.5x magnifications with your choice of two frame styles and each ship with TWO pair of silicone eyecups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEW MicroEF Scopes</title>
      <link>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/hygienists/new-micro-ef-scopes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/hygienists/new-micro-ef-scopes/</guid>
      <description>Revolutionary Prismatic Design
Up to 50% Smaller Up to 44% Lighter Designs for Vision Custom Optics with rectangular shape for maximum peripheral vision.
Provide a 50% increase in the Field of View over the Standard Field of the same magnification. These Surgical Telescopes provide crisp side to side imaging for procedures where a wider field of view is required.
See what they are saying about the award winning Micro Series Scopes:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Panoramic Loupes</title>
      <link>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/hygienists/new-panoramic-loupes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/hygienists/new-panoramic-loupes/</guid>
      <description>See Beyond Expanded Field Loupes See BEYOND expanded field with the patented panoramic design – the first advancement in telescopic optics in 100 years
Doubles the Viewable Area over Prismatic Expanded Field optics, and more than quadruples the viewable area over Galilean Standard Field optics
3.5x and 4.5x Precision Magnification available with unprecedented fields of view
Designs for Vision Custom Optics with crisp side to side imaging and rectangular shape for maximum peripheral vision</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Student Guide</title>
      <link>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/hygienists/student-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/hygienists/student-guide/</guid>
      <description>Read our Student Guide: Click here
Student Loupe Experiences WHY MAGNIFICATION “Dental magnification loupes significantly enhanced student performance during preclinical dental education and were considered an effective adjunct by the students who used them.” (Quintessence International, January 2011 Volume 42 , Issue 1)
Magnification provides the ergonomic and clinical benefit of purchasing dental loupes. Not all loupes provide the same magnification. Compare:
For more info click here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working without Magnification</title>
      <link>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/hygienists/working-without-magnification/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bharatgrowthconsultants.com/dental/hygienists/working-without-magnification/</guid>
      <description>CAUSES Fatigue, Eye Strain, Neck Pain, Lower Back Pain Designs for Vision&amp;rsquo;s Precision Coated Magnification not only improves your vision and patient care, it reduces these problems attributed to poor posture.
Read Abstracts of Clinical Studies:
Effect of magnification loupes on dental hygiene student posture –JP Maillet</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
