<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hygienists on Bharat growth Consultants</title>
    <link>http://vipatra.in/dental/hygienists/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hygienists on Bharat growth Consultants</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://vipatra.in/dental/hygienists/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2.5x Designer Telescopes</title>
      <link>http://vipatra.in/dental/hygienists/2.5x-designer-telescopes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vipatra.in/dental/hygienists/2.5x-designer-telescopes/</guid>
      <description>True 2.5X Magnification Though some companies claim that magnification is not important, it is the most important feature of a magnification system. A system that magnifies the image only 2.0x reduces the users ability to visualize structures by a factor of 25%. Designs for Vision produces accurate precision magnification with maximum resolution.
Thru-the-Lens (TTL) Optics This lightweight system provides the Widest Field of View
Ergonomically Correct – Made for YOUR eyes ONLY Built to your Interpupillary Distance instead of one size fits all, these telescopes Incorporate your eyeglass prescription into both the carrier lens and the telescope.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BDR Loupes</title>
      <link>http://vipatra.in/dental/hygienists/bdr-loupes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vipatra.in/dental/hygienists/bdr-loupes/</guid>
      <description>Best Resolution Our precision coated optics with true magnification reduces eye strain by providing the best resolution and&amp;hellip;
Greatest Depth of Field Contributing to the prevention of neck and lower back pain. Widest Field of View BDR Loupes provide TRUE Magnification and the widest field of view.
Unobstructed View We manufacture the only rectangular optics providing an unobstructive view.
Lightest Weight Comfortable, Hypoallergenic, Lightweight Frames
Easiest to Clean </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frame Selection Guide</title>
      <link>http://vipatra.in/dental/hygienists/frame-selection-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vipatra.in/dental/hygienists/frame-selection-guide/</guid>
      <description>NEW Disinfection Information: NEW Disinfectable Eyewear Retainers available for your Loupes
Disinfecting Instructions for Loupes and Headlights</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Micro 2.5x Scopes</title>
      <link>http://vipatra.in/dental/hygienists/new-micro2.5x-scopes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vipatra.in/dental/hygienists/new-micro2.5x-scopes/</guid>
      <description>23% Smaller, 36% Lighter allowing for increased peripheral vision and lightweight comfort
True 2.5x Magnification Engineered for dentists and hygienists that require true 2.5X magnification, but request a lighter, smaller device.
Ergonomically Correct – Made for YOUR eyes ONLY Designs for Vision matches the focal length of each telescope to YOUR ideal working distance, customizing the depth of focus for maximum ergonomics.
Unmatched Quality and Performance Precision coated for the sharpest and clearest magnified image - Better than HD they are precision optics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEW High Definition Imaging – HDi</title>
      <link>http://vipatra.in/dental/hygienists/new-high-definition-imaging/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vipatra.in/dental/hygienists/new-high-definition-imaging/</guid>
      <description>NEW High Definition Imaging – HDi Introducing HDi&amp;rsquo;s advanced photonic design providing uniform light distribution with fiber optic quality light. The entire LED DayLite® series of headlights, Corded and WireLess, are now equipped with HDi technology providing 45% more light and increased modularity.
HDi - High Definition Imaging HDI with optically focused LED Uniform Light Distribution advanced photonic design perfectly images LED for uniform light distribution with maximum intensity
More Illumination optically focused LED provides 45% more light</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working without Magnification</title>
      <link>http://vipatra.in/dental/hygienists/working-without-magnification/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vipatra.in/dental/hygienists/working-without-magnification/</guid>
      <description>CAUSES Fatigue, Eye Strain, Neck Pain, Lower Back Pain Designs for Vision&amp;rsquo;s Precision Coated Magnification not only improves your vision and patient care, it reduces these problems attributed to poor posture.
Read Abstracts of Clinical Studies:
Effect of magnification loupes on dental hygiene student posture –JP Maillet</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
